<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ghidra on Lum8rjack</title>
    <link>https://blog.lum8rjack.com/tags/ghidra/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ghidra on Lum8rjack</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.lum8rjack.com/tags/ghidra/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Function Hooking Part 2 - Password Safe</title>
      <link>https://blog.lum8rjack.com/posts/function-hooking-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.lum8rjack.com/posts/function-hooking-part-2/</guid>
      
      <description>In this post I will expand on the information from my first post, Function Hooking Part 1 - Test Program. Previously, I discussed hooking a function from a custom application, in this post I will be hooking a function in the open-source password manager Password Safe.
As you can image, password managers are valuable targets during red team engaments since they contain additional credentials for other services or computers. If the main password to open the database is known or obtained, then all of the other credentials in the database are compromised.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Function Hooking Part 1 - Test Program</title>
      <link>https://blog.lum8rjack.com/posts/function-hooking-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.lum8rjack.com/posts/function-hooking-part-1/</guid>
      
      <description>I have recently been spending time learning more about reverse engineering and patching applications including fixing older programs that I do not have the source code for. I&amp;rsquo;ve started looking into function hooking and identifying how it works and different scenarios I could use it. There are a ton of articles online but most of them do not provide simple examples for starters or are focused on Windows API. While Windows API hooking is useful, I am more interested in hooking higher level functions.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Engineering C3000Z</title>
      <link>https://blog.lum8rjack.com/posts/c3000z/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.lum8rjack.com/posts/c3000z/</guid>
      
      <description>The following post goes through the steps I took to reverse engineer different binaries in routers with the goal of decrypting an encoded password.
I recently switched internet providers and was given a new modem/router. When the technician came to setup my service, the device was already configured and just needed plugged in. I was planning on switching out the device with my old router, since I already had firewall rules and static routes configured, however when I logged into the new device I noticed it was configured to use PPoE to connect to the ISP.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
